And how long are we going to sit here focusing on trying to get reparations?
It's been how many years since slavery?
150 years?
1865?
Whenever there is a real thing that this country wants to do, they do it.
Okay.
Well, first I'll start with, it will help on even just a moral level.
The reality is that the United States has become very comfortable with the fact that
it does not consider black people equal.
And it shows that in many ways that I'm sure we will discuss over the course of today.
But ultimately, there has not been a committed, concerted effort to shifting the mindset around
the use of black people as a labor force in this nation back when it was slavery, now in
the voice, in the use of slavery as slave labor in prisons.
So on a basic cultural level, reparations are an act of repair.
They are an effort to say, Arbat, we see you now.
We have seen that done with Japanese folks who were put in internment camps.
We have seen that done with Jewish folks.
We have seen that done even in the case of slave owners who received reparations.
When it comes to the use of tax dollars to pay reparations, and this is going to come
up a lot today, it's a matter of values, right?
For me, my value system circulates around the fact that I think that as a community, we
should all be engaged in repair for our community.
So I don't think there should be any problem with there being tax dollars spent at repairing
consistent efforts that have been made to impede black people.